Guide to the Records of the North American Jewish Students Appeal, undated, 1962, 1964-1996 (bulk 1971-1995) *I-338 and *I-338A
Center for Jewish History, Publisher.
- Series V: Federations, undated, 1971-1995; Boxes 61 (Folders 25-30) - Box 94.
  - Subseries 1: Council of Jewish Federations (CJF), undated, 1971-1995; Box 61 (Folders 25-30) - 64 (Folders 1-3).
    In 1990, the National Funding Council (NFC), an UJC-sponsored council similar in structure to the LCBC, began reviewing and certifying the APPEAL's budgetary process. Box 63, Folders 1 and 2 contains NAJSA budgets, Constituent Reviews, planning and preparation documents regarding the NFC
    - Budget Digest Drafts and Correspondence, 1974-1980 (Box 61, Folder 25)
    - College Youth and Faculty Programs Committee, 1975-1976 (Box 61, Folder 26)
    - College Youth and Faculty Programs Committee, 1979-1980, 1982, 1988 (Box 61, Folder 27)
    - General Files and Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 61, Folder 28)
    - General Files and Correspondence, 1973 (Box 61, Folder 29)
    - General Files and Correspondence, 1974 (Box 61, Folder 30)
    - General Files and Correspondence, 1975 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - General Files and Correspondence, 1976 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - General Files and Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - General Files and Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - General Files and Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - General Files and Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - General Files and Correspondence, 1986 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - General Files and Correspondence, 1987-1989 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - General Files and Correspondence, 1990-1995 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Leadership Development Committee Workshop Materials "Leadership and the Decision-Making Process: A Core Study Approach", [1976] (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - National Funding Council (NFC) Budget and Constituent Reviews, undated, 1990-1993 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - National Funding Council (NFC) Planning and Preparation, 1993-1995 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Quarterly Board/Committee Planning Meeting, 1976 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Quarterly Board/Committee Planning Meeting, 1977 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Quarterly Board/Committee Planning Meeting, 1978-1979 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Quarterly Board/Committee Planning Meeting, 1983 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Quarterly Board/Committee Planning Meeting and Trustee Meeting, 1987 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Quarterly Board/Committee Planning Meeting, 1988 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Quarterly Board/Committee Planning Meeting and Trustee Meeting, 1989 (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Quarterly Board/Committee Planning Meeting, 1990 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Quarterly Board/Committee Planning Meeting, 1991-1992 (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - Quarterly Board/Committee Planning Meeting, 1993 (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - Task Force on Services to Jewish University Students, 1991-1993 (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - Task Force on Services to Jewish University Students, 1993 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Task Force on Services to Jewish University Students, 1993-1994 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Women's Committee on Russian Women, 1978-1979 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 2: General Assembly (GA), 1972-1994; Box 64 (Folders 4-11) - Box 66 (Folders 1-5).
    The Subseries is arranged in chronological order.
    The documents of the General Assembly subseries represent the NAJSA's participation in the annually held event of the CJF. The subseries primarily contains materials regarding the conferences such as agendas, programs, speeches, schedules, and travel and hotel arrangements. Although these types of documents are the predominant materials, correspondence and memos concerning the General Assembly meetings (throughout the specified year) are included, along with some handwritten notes of meetings attended. Photographs of the APPEAL's participation in the 1987 General Assembly may be found in Series IX: Photographs,Box 112, Folder 16.
    - Conference Materials (41st Annual, Toronto, Canada, November 8-12), 1972 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Arrangements and Conference Materials (42nd Annual, New Orleans, LA, November 8-11), 1973 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Committee on College Youth and Faculty Programs Speeches and Correspondence (43rd Annual, Chicago, IL, November 12-17), 1974 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, Conference Materials, Arrangements and Itineraries (44th Annual, Miami, FL, November 19-23) (1 of 2), 1975 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Committee and Conference Planning Drafts (2 of 2), 1975 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, Conference Materials and Itineraries (45th Annual, Philadelphia, PA, November 9-14), 1976 (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence and Conference Materials (46th Annual, Dallas, TX, November 9-13), 1977 (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence and Conference Materials (48th Annual, San Francisco, CA, November 8-12, 1979), 1978-1979 (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence and Memos (49th Annual, Detroit, MI, November 12-16, 1980), 1979-1980 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Accommodation Arrangements and Brochure (50th Annual, St. Louis, MO, November 10-15), 1981 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Conference Materials, Student Handbook, Schedule, Ephemera and Alphabetical Listing of Presidents and Executive Directors (51st Annual, Los Angeles, CA, November 10-15), [1982] (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Conference Materials and Correspondence (52nd Annual, Atlanta, GA, November 15-20), 1983 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - College Services Committee and General Assembly Conference Materials (Washington, DC, May 1984 and 53rd Annual, Toronto, CA, November 12-16) (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Conference Materials (54th Annual, Washington, DC, November 12-17), 1985 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Arrangements and Federation Listings (55rd Annual, Chicago, IL, November 12-16), 1986 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Conference Materials, Memos and Arrangements (56th Annual, Miami, FL, November 18-22), 1987 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Conference Materials, Correspondence, Memos and Arrangements (57th Annual, New Orleans, LA, November 16-19), 1988 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Conference Materials, Correspondence, Memos, Arrangements and Evaluations (58th Annual, Cincinnati, OH, November 14-19), 1989 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Conference Materials, Evaluations, Arrangements and Notes (59th Annual, San Francisco, CA, November 13-18), 1990 (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence and Memos (59th Annual, San Francisco, CA, November 13-18), 1990 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Conference Materials, Correspondence and Memos (60th Annual, Baltimore, MD, November 19-24), 1991 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Conference Materials, Correspondence and Memos (61st Annual, New York, NY, November 10-15), 1992 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Conference Materials, Correspondence, Memos, Arrangements and Notes (62nd Annual, Montreal, CA, November 16-21), 1993 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Conference Materials, Correspondence and Memos (63rd Annual, Denver, CO, November 15-21), 1994 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 3: Large City Budgeting Conference (LCBC), undated, 1971-1995; Box 66 (Folders 6-11) - Box 70 (Folders 1-4).
    The Large City Budgeting Council subseries represents the NAJSA's formulation of budgets, budgeting guidelines, and the budgeting process as presented and approved by the LCBC at the General Assembly. The bulk of the materials in this subseries consist of financial documentation, budget formulation, correspondence, memos and meeting agendas (Box 66, Folder 9-11 to Box 69, Folders 1-4). NAJSA Budget Digests prepared by the LCBC for distribution to Federations may be found in Box 69, Folder 5 for the years 1975-1995. Box 69, Folder 7 contains an LCBC committee review of the APPEAL to determine the justification of a budgetary increase for the APPEAL. Other items of interest include the APPEAL's 'descriptive narratives,' primarily an overview of the activities, history and needs of the APPEAL and their constituents presented to the LCBC (Box 70, Folder 1) each year as part of the budget process. In 1993, the LCBC was abolished and restructured under the National Funding Council (NFC). See Box 63, Folders 1 and 2 for information regarding the APPEAL's attempt to obtain funding status from the NFC. The attempt failed and ultimately was one of the contributing factors of the dismantling of the APPEAL as Federation allocation funds shrank overall.
    - APPEAL Audits, 1970s, 1980s (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Audit Guidelines, 1971, 1976 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Beneficiary Agencies, undated, 1989 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Budget Certification Process, 1975-1976 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Budget Certification Process (1of 2), 1976-1977 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Budget Certification Process (2 of 2), 1976-1977 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Budget Certification Process, 1977-1978 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Budget Certification Process, 1978-1979 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Budget Certification Process, 1979-1980 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Budget Certification Process, 1980-1981 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Budget Certification Process, 1981-1982 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Budget Certification Process, 1983-1984 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Budget Certification Process, 1984-1985 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Budget Certification Process, 1985-1986 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Budget Certification Process, 1986-1987 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Budget Certification Process (1 of 2), 1987-1988 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Budget Certification Process (2 of 2), 1987-1988 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Budget Certification Process, 1989-1990 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Budget Certification Process, 1990-1991 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Budget Certification Process, 1991-1992 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Budget Certification Process (1 of 2), 1992-1993 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Budget Certification Process (2 of 2), 1992-1993 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Budget Digests, 1975-1992 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Budget Review Series-Other Agencies, 1976-1977 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Committee Review of the NAJSA, 1981-1983 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Descriptive Narratives, 1977-1995 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - "Fair Share" Allocation Hearings Worksheets, 1977-1980 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Joint Cultural Appeal LCBC Budgets, 1972-1974, 1976-1977 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Minutes of the LCBC and Conference Description, 1970s, 1980s (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 4: United Jewish Appeal (UJA), 1971-1980, 1988, 1990-1994; Box 70 (Folders 5-11) - Box 71 (Folders 1-6).
    The UJA, as part of the Federation distribution process, appears in this series. Primarily the subseries consists of correspondence regarding the NAJSA and the Young Leadership Cabinet (YLC) of the UJA, including some early letters between YLC members and NAJSA trustees in the pursuit of acquiring Federation recognition and funding (Box 70, Folder 10). The Young Leadership Cabinet, along with B'nai B'rith Hillel, held some responsibility in formulating a somewhat united front on matters of the Jewish community response to college age youth and campus programming. As a slightly more radical and somewhat more flexible organization, the NAJSA conflicted with or over lapped on, campus programming concerns between the UJA and Hillel. This conflict brought some tension between the NAJSA and the YLC, which is reflected in correspondence from 1976 (Box 70, Folder 6 and 5). Correspondence between Ms. Dessel and UJA Executive Vice Chairman Irving Bernstein, includes a lively letter exchange regarding an article written by Dessel, Michael Pelavin and Steven Schwartz regarding their view of the UJA, among other correspondence between Dessel and Bernstein. Additional Hillel materials can be found in Series II: Subseries 1, Organizational Records,Box 21, Folders 3-11 and Box 22, Folders 1-3.
    - Brochures and Conference Programs, 1975, [1990-1994] (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1972, 1974-1975 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1976-1980, 1988 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence and Memos, 1990-1994 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Student Advisory Board Member Lists and Memo, 1977-1978 (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - United Jewish Students Appeal Correspondence, 1971-1973 (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - University Programs Campaign Manual, 1993 (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - Young Leadership Cabinet Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Young Leadership Cabinet Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Young Leadership Cabinet Correspondence, 1974-1978, 1980, 1991 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Young Leadership Cabinet Directories, 1971-1973 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Young Leadership Cabinet Directories, 1974-1975 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Young Leadership Cabinet Graduate Mailing, 1978 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Subseries 5: United States Cities and Canada, undated, 1971-1995; Box 71 (Folders 7-11) - Box 94 (Folders 1-8).
    Original folders within this subseries filed materials from the Federations individually by community. For the purpose of archiving the collection, communities were combined into folders for long-term storage. If more than two communities appear within a given folder, a hyphen separates each initial community. If only two cities appear within folders, the word 'and' is used. For example, Bergen County, NJ - Boise, ID indicates that one or more cities or towns are alphabetically located between Bergen and Boise within that folder. Ann Arbor, MI and Asheville, NC, denotes that only these cities are included within the folder. In cases where more than two communities appear as the folder title, the locations are written on the front of the folder. Box 71, Folders 7-9, containing Federation documentation and memos, are arranged in alphabetical order.
    The final piece of the Federation puzzle structure lays in the relationship between the NAJSA and the Federations located in communities based upon population size (classified as large, intermediate, and small) and the Canadian local Federation system (primarily Montreal and Toronto). Subseries 5 documents the working relationship between the Federations, and the NAJSA (and its Trustees) in making, maintaining and keeping lines of communication open between the APPEAL and the Federations. In addition, the process of funds allocation from the Federations to the APPEAL is contained within this subseries. (See also Series II, Subseries 2: Financial Records for compiled lists of funds allocated from each of the Federations to the APPEAL by year.)
    The files within this subseries generally follow the same pattern. A ledger sheet is present for each city or town recording the Federation's annual allocation and when it was received. The remainder of the materials within the files contain correspondence, memos, solicitation materials, APPEAL narratives, check stubs and Federation information. Letters to NAJSA Trustees asking for help in appealing to their local Federation are also included within the files.
    - Guidelines and Due Dates, 1994 (Box 71, Folder 7)
    - Form Letter Samples, undated (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Memos, 1975-1976, 1979-1981 (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - Akron, OH and Albany, NY, 1971-1995 (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - Albuquerque, NM and Alexandria, LA, 1971-1995 (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - Allentown and Altoona, PA, 1971-1995 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Ann Arbor, MI and Asheville, NC, 1971-1995 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Atlanta, GA, 1971-1990 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Atlanta, GA, 1991-1995 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Atlantic County, NJ, 1972-1995 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Augusta, GA - Avenel, NJ, 1972-1995 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Baltimore, MD, 1971-1995 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Bangor, ME - Belleville, IL, 1972-1985 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Bangor, ME - Belleville, IL, 1986-1995 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Bergen County, NJ - Boise, ID, 1971-1979 (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Bergen County, NJ - Boise, ID, 1980-1987 (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Bergen County, NJ - Boise, ID, 1988-1995 (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Boston, MA, 1971 - 1982 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Boston, MA, 1983 - 1995 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Brevard County, FL - Bridgewater (Somerset County), NJ, 1972-1995 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Brockton, MA - Butler, PA, 1971-1980 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Brockton, MA - Butler, PA, 1981-1995 (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Canadian Federations, 1976-1977, 1989-1991, 1994 (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - Canton, OH - Cedar Rapids, IA, 1972-1995 (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Central Florida - Champaign-Urbana, IL, 1986-1995 (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Central Florida - Champaign-Urbana, IL, 1986-1995 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Chapel Hill, NC - Charleston, WV, 1972-1995 (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Charlotte, NC - Cherry Hill (Camden County), NJ, 1972-1981 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Charlotte, NC - Cherry Hill (Camden County), NJ, 1982-1995 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Chicago, IL, 1972-1978 (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Chicago, IL, 1980-1995 (Box 75, Folder 7)
    - Cincinnati, OH and Clearwater, FL, 1971-1979 (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - Cincinnati, OH and Clearwater, FL, 1980-1995 (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Cleveland, OH, 1971-1977 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Cleveland, OH, 1978-1985 (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Cleveland, OH, 1986-1990 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Cleveland, OH, 1991-1995 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Clifton-Passaic, NJ - Columbus, GA, 1971-1995 (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Columbus, OH, 1971-1985 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Columbus, OH, 1986-1995 (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Corpus Christi, TX - Cumberland County, NJ, 1972-1995 (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Dallas, TX, 1971-1979 (Box 77, Folder 4)
    - Dallas, TX, 1980-1987 (Box 77, Folder 5)
    - Dallas, TX, 1988-1995 (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - Danbury, CT and Davenport, IA, 1972-1995 (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Dayton, OH and Deal Park, NJ, 1971-1995 (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - Decatur, IL and Delaware (Wilmington, DE), 1972-1995 (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Denver, CO, 1971-1995 (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Des Moines, IA, 1971-1995 (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Detroit, MI, 1971-1984 (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Detroit, MI, 1985-1995 (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Duluth, MN and Dutchess County (Poughkeepsie), NY, 1972-1995 (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - East St. Louis (Southern Illinois), IL - Elgin, IL, 1972-1995 (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - Elmira, NY and El Paso, TX, 1971-1995 (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Englewood, NJ and Erie, PA, 1971-1995 (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Essexville (Bay City) MI - Fall River, MA, 1972-1995 (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Flint, MI, 1972-1995 (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - Fitchburg, MA and Florence, AL, 1977-1987 (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - Ft. Lauderdale, FL, 1972-1995 (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - Fort Wayne, IN, 1972-1995 (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - Fort Worth, TX, 1972-1994 (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - Framingham, MA and Galveston, TX, 1972-1995 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Garden Grove (Orange County), CA - Glens Falls, NY, 1972-1987 (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Grand Rapids, MI and Green Bay, WI, 1972-1995 (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Greensboro, TN and Greenwich, CT, 1972-1995 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Harrisburg, PA, 1971-1994 (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Hartford, CT, 1971-1988 (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Hartford, CT, 1988-1995 (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Haverhill, MA - Highland (Northwest Indiana), IN, 1974-1995 (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Hollywood (South Broward), FL - Honolulu, HI, 1971-1983 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Hollywood (South Broward), FL - Honolulu, HI, 1984-1995 (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Houston, TX, 1971-1982 (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Houston, TX, 1983-1995 (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - Hudson, NY and Huntington, WV, 1972-1987 (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - Indianapolis, IN, 1971-1994 (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - Jackson, MS and Jacksonville, FL, 1972-1995 (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - Jersey City, NJ - Joliet, IL, 1971-1995 (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - Kalamazoo, MI and Kansas City, KS, 1971-1995 (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - Kenosha, WI - Knoxville, TN, 1972-1995 (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - Lafayette, IN and Lakewood, NJ, 1972-1995 (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - Lancaster, PA - Las Vegas, NV, 1971-1995 (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - Lawrence, MA - Leominster, MA, 1972-1995 (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - Levittown, PA - Lexington, KY, 1972-1995 (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - Lima, OH - Little Rock, AR, 1972-1995 (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - Long Beach, CA, 1971-1995 (Box 82, Folder 8)
    - Los Angeles, CA, 1971-1975 (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Los Angeles, CA, 1976-1979 (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - Los Angeles, CA, 1980-1985 (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - Los Angeles, CA, 1986-1986 (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - Los Angeles, CA, 1990-1995 (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - Louisville, KY, 1971-1995 (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - Madison, WI - Marblehead, MA, 1971-1995 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Memphis, TN - Merrimack Valley, MA, 1971-1995 (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - Metro West, NJ, 1971-1979 (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Metro West, NJ, 1980-1987 (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - Metro West, NJ, 1988-1995 (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - Miami, FL, 1971-1984 (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - Miami, FL, 1985-1995 (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - Michigan City, IN - Middlesex (Edison) County, NJ, 1972-1995 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Milwaukee, WI, 1971-1984 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - Milwaukee, WI, 1985-1995 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - Minneapolis, MN, 1970-1995 (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - Mobile, AL and Monmouth (Deal) County, NJ, 1971-1995 (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - Monroe, LA - Muncie, IN, 1972-1995 (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - Nashville, TN, 1971-1995 (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - New Bedford (North Dartmouth), MA - New Castle, PA, 1971-1987 (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - New Haven, CT and New London, CT, 1971-1995 (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - New Orleans, LA, 1971-1994 (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - New York, NY, 1975-1994 (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - Newburgh, NY and Newport News, VA, 1971-1995 (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - Niagara Falls, NY - Norristown, PA, 1972-1995 (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - North Dartmouth, MA and North Jersey (Wayne), NJ, 1981-1995 (Box 86, Folder 7)
    - Northwestern NY and Norwalk, CT, 1971-1995 (Box 86, Folder 8)
    - Oakland, CA, 1971-1995 (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - Oklahoma City, OK, 1971-1995 (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - Omaha, NE, 1971-1995 (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - Orange County (See Garden Grove, CA)
    - Orlando, FL and Ormond Beach (Volusia and Flagler Counties), FL, 1976-1995 (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - Palm Beach, FL and Palm Springs, CA, 1975-1995 (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - Passaic, NJ - Perth Amboy, NJ, 1972-1995 (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - Philadelphia, PA, 1971-1980 (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - Philadelphia, PA, 1981-1987 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Philadelphia, PA, 1988-1995 (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - Phoenix, AZ, 1971-1995 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - Pinellas (Clearwater) County, FL and Pittsburgh, PA, 1971-1982 (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - Pinellas (Clearwater) County, FL and Pittsburgh, PA, 1983-1995 (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - Pittsfield (Berkshires), MA and Port Chester, NY, 1972-1995 (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - Portland, ME, 1972-1995 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - Portland, OR, 1971-1995 (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - Portsmouth, VA - Princeton, NJ, 1972-1987, 1992-1995 (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - Providence, RI, 1971-1985 (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - Providence, RI, 1986-1995 (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - Quad Cities (Rock Island), IL, 1972-1982 (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - Racine, WI - Reading, PA, 1971-1995 (Box 89, Folder 7)
    - Richmond, VA, 1971-1995 (Box 89, Folder 8)
    - Roanoke, VA and Rochester, NY, 1971-1980 (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - Roanoke, VA and Rochester, NY, 1981-1995 (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - Rockford, IL and Rockland City, NY, 1972-1995 (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - Sacramento, CA and Saginaw, MI, 1972-1995 (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - Saint Joseph, MO and Saint Louis, MO, 1971-1979 (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - Saint Joseph, MO and Saint Louis, MO, 1980-1995 (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - Saint Paul, MN and St. Petersburg, FL, 1971-1995 (Box 90, Folder 7)
    - Salt Lake City, UT and San Antonio, TX, 1971-1995 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - San Bernardino, CA and San Diego, CA, 1971-1995 (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - San Francisco, CA, 1971-1979 (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - San Francisco, CA, 1980-1986 (Box 91, Folder 4)